A Guide to the Office of the Vice-President, Louis A. Pardue Records, 1950-1963
Special Collections, Virginia Tech
- ORINS, 1945-1971
  - ORINS, University Relations, 1959 (Box 24, Folder 1069)
  - ORINS, University Relations, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 1070)
  - ORINS, University Relations, 1971 (Box 24, Folder 1071)
  - ORINS, VPI Considers Membership in ORINS, 1946 (Box 24, Folder 1072)